CV - Gustav Bøgh

About me

Hello, I'm Gustav Bøgh, a 25-year-old multimedia design student with a focus on web development and digital marketing. My experience includes Frontend coding as well as Digital Marketing. I am enthusiastic about implementing effective Marketing Strategies and Web Solutions. I am dedicated to contributing to the development of online profiles, branding, and communication. I am seeking an opportunity where I can blend my frontend skills with my passion for digital marketing to make an impact.

Some of my projects

Student job:

 Oak | 8 – Instagram and Facebook SoMe Marketing presentation campaign https://www.instagram.com/oak8dk/ - https://www.facebook.com/oak8dk

1. Semester projects:

https://portfolio-gustavboegh.netlify.app/

2. Semester projects:

 https://ux-copenhagenteam1.netlify.app/

- https://vildmad2sem.netlify.app/
- https://ca-kampagnesite.netlify.app/
- https://javaguitarscph.netlify.app/

3. Semester (Frontend) projects:

https://github.com/Gust0288

Video projects:

- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gEEXFLcVn3Y
- https://www.youtube.com/shorts/07kKNwjjKCY
- https://youtu.be/IVPgt-aQVQ0

.

Skills

Web development:

- HTML/CSS Advanced
- JavaScript Advanced
- JavaScript API handling— Advanced
- React Framework Intermediate
- Java Basic

- SQL Basic
- Responsive Web Design Advanced
- Astro Framework Advanced
- Database handling (Supabase, MySQL) Advanced
- Motion Design Basic

Design/CMS tools:

- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, InDesign) Intermediate
- Figma Advanced
- WordPress Basic

Graphical design:

- Typography Basic
- Color theory Basic
- Layout design Intermediate

Multimedia production:

- Video editing (e.g., Adobe Premiere Pro) Advanced
- Video production (Sony, Canon etc.) Intermediate
- Sound editing (e.g., Adobe Audition) Basic

User Experience Design (UX):

• User testing - Advanced

CV - Gustav Bøgh

- Wireframing Advanced
- Prototyping Advanced
- User experience testing Advanced

Marketing and Communication:

- Business model canvas (BMC) Intermediate
- SWOT Intermediate
- Value Proposition Canvas (VPC) -Intermediate
- Data and SoMe Analytics (Google Analytics)
 Intermediate
- Google Ads Intermediate

- Meta (Business suite/Ad manager) ads Intermediate
- Key Performance Indicators (KPI's) Intermediate
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Intermediate

Personal Qualifications

- Independent
- Passioned

- Flexible
- Ambitious

Work Experience

| Year | Profession | Where | |
|-------------|---------------------------------------|---|--|
| 2024 - now | Marketing Assistant/Student Assistant | Oak 8, Hellerup | |
| 2024 - now | Marketing Assistant/Student Assistant | Maleea, Hellerup | |
| 2023 | Video Producer/Editor/Director | Oles Hus (Coffee and Wine Bar), Gentofte | |
| 2023 | Multimedia Design Student | Copenhagen School of Design and Technology, | |
| | | Copenhagen | |
| 2020 - 2024 | Bartender | Oles Hus (Coffee and Wine Bar), Gentofte | |
| 2020 | Restaurant All-rounder | The Landing, Honeysuckle Dr, Newcastle NSW, | |
| | | Australia | |
| 2019 | Bartender | Victoria Pub, Gammeltorv, Copenhagen | |
| 2019 | Bartender | Royal Arena (Concert Hall) VIP Lounge | |
| 2016 - 2019 | Bartender and Waiter | Chabber.com (freelance waiter) | |
| 2018 | Bartender and Waiter | Tribeca, Nørrebro, Copenhagen | |
| 2017 - 2018 | Lodge Waiter and Bartender | Odd Fellow Palæet, Copenhagen | |
| 2016 - 2017 | Leader/Key holder | LokalBrugsen, Virum | |
| 2015 - 2016 | Check-out Assistant | Fakta (supermarket), Kongens Lyngby | |

Education

| Year | School | Education/Degree | City |
|-------------|---|---|------------|
| 2023 - now | Copenhagen School of Design and Technology | Multimedia Design | Copenhagen |
| 2021 - 2022 | Copenhagen Business Academy (3 Semesters) | Computer Science | Copenhagen |
| 2018 - 2019 | Sergeant School – Danish Military (7 Months) | Sergeant (Non-commissioned officer) | Varde |
| 2018 | Aalborg Kaserne | National Military Service (Værnepligt) | Aalborg |
| 2015 - 2018 | Virum Gymnasium | Graduate | Virum |
| 2014 - 2015 | Kerteminde Boarding School | 10th grade | Kerteminde |
| 2004 - 2014 | Kongevejens Skole | 0-9th grade | Virum |

Languages Danish (Native), English (Fluently), Norwegian (Conversational)